<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Don't Touch My Mushroom</title>
 <link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <id>http://localhost:4000</id>
 <updated>2021-09-06T00:09:38+00:00</updated>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <uri></uri>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 

 <entry>
   <title>A new life!</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/new_life"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/new_life</id>
   <updated>2021-09-30T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The mushrooms are back on 2021!
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members! Come for a fantastical time full of unexpected surprises.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Improfight: Don't Touch My Mushroom VS Dodecahedron</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/fight_dodecahedron"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/fight_dodecahedron</id>
   <updated>2020-10-29T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;massage-box alert-warning&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-exclamation-triangle&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This show has been cancelled due to COVID19. &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;p&gt;We will see you on stage again in 2021!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;!--more--&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our impro fight will set two impro groups face to face on stage and make them compete for more applause from the audience....</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Theater Sports by ZIC: DTMM VS ZIC</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/ZIC_theater_sports"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/ZIC_theater_sports</id>
   <updated>2020-10-08T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt; is organizing a theater sports show and they invited us to participate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!--more--&gt; &lt;p&gt;Team against team – improviser against improviser – Titan against Titan!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The home team, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt;, competes in each show against a different improv group from Switzerland. The two...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>The Harold</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/the_harold"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/the_harold</id>
   <updated>2020-09-17T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Harold is a longform improvised format which emphasises patterns, themes and group discoveries instead of a traditional plot or story. Everything starts from a simple suggestion from the audience. &lt;!--more--&gt; The &lt;strong&gt;Game&lt;/strong&gt; of the scene is not predetermined. We create Games and their rules in the moment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Doors open...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>First online Improv show</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/first_online_show"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/first_online_show</id>
   <updated>2020-05-09T21:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No virus is going to prevent us from doing what we like most! Don’t Touch My Mushroom adapts to the circumstances and brings us a fully online improv show experience.&lt;!--more--&gt; We might face a pandemic, technical difficulties and a confinement, but we hope we can bring a smile to your...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Online workshop: One offer at a time</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/stephen"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/stephen</id>
   <updated>2020-03-24T19:30:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;No virus is going to keep us from doing Improv! Now that most of us are secluded at home we should adapt and do things that keep us sane.&lt;!--more--&gt; I would go insane without improv and so we decided to contact international improvisers to give us workshops through VC. The...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Your body can create 1001 characters!</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/cedric2"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/cedric2</id>
   <updated>2020-02-23T10:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Change your voice, play with your face, transform your attitude, your body is a formidable metamorphosing tool!.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Through guided exercises based on Lecoq’s work, we will discover the power of every muscle and the thousand forms your body can take to personify characters you didn’t imagine playing. They are all...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Mime and object work</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/cedric1"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/cedric1</id>
   <updated>2020-02-22T10:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This workshop focuses on a side-skill : miming and object and space work.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Having a clear vision of your environment, the objects and furnitures that are around, the size and weight of the mimes you use, is an helpful friend to make your stories more true to you, your partners...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Mushrooms on Stage</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/mushroom-on-stage"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/mushroom-on-stage</id>
   <updated>2020-02-20T20:00:01+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members! You will not walk out smarter, but you will walk out happier! &lt;!--more--&gt; Doors open at 19:50. Show duration 20:00 -&amp;gt;...</content>
 </entry>

 

 <entry>
   <title>Wombats vs Mushrooms - Impro Battle</title>
   <link href="http://localhost:4000/wombats-battle"/>
   <id>http://localhost:4000/wombats-battle</id>
   <updated>2020-01-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The prophecy says that in 2020 a new generation of improv show will emerge. Only the bravest improvisers will dare challenge the mighty &lt;strong&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/strong&gt;. In this first edition, the &lt;strong&gt;Wisdom of Wombats&lt;/strong&gt; have answered the calling. Who will become the winner of the first &lt;strong&gt;Improv Battle&lt;/strong&gt;? &lt;!--more--&gt;...</content>
 </entry>

 

</feed>