<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-02-04T00:10:23+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Don’t Touch My Mushroom</title><subtitle>&quot;Don't Touch My Mushroom&quot; is an improvisional theatre company that grows &amp; performs in Zurich, Switzerland. Despite not having a single native speaker, we proudly perform in English with a wide variety accents and oddities.
</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><entry><title type="html">Improv is Back</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/impro-is-back" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Improv is Back" /><published>2024-04-19T19:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-19T19:30:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/impro-is-back</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/impro-is-back">&lt;p&gt;Let’s celebrate the return of IMPROV to jenseits IM VIADUKT&lt;!--more--&gt;  with a glorious double feature of English improv and musical improv! &lt;a href=&quot;https://dont-tou.ch&quot;&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/a&gt; present a surprising fully improvised theatre show with scenes never seen before. Emotions, drama, fun and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;«&lt;a href=&quot;https://basicpit.ch&quot;&gt;Basic Pitches&lt;/a&gt;» present a musical show like no other! Basic Pitches will improvise an entire musical, complete with chart topping songs, from a few audience suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out on a truly imaginative, funny, touching, co-created and most of all enjoyable evening.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><summary type="html">Let’s celebrate the return of IMPROV to jenseits IM VIADUKT</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Double feature - Basic Pitches: Pitch us a Musical &amp;amp; DTMM: Shiitake Happens</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dynamo_mar_2024" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Double feature - Basic Pitches: Pitch us a Musical &amp;amp; DTMM: Shiitake Happens" /><published>2024-03-20T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-20T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dynamo_mar_2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dynamo_mar_2024">&lt;p&gt;Come and enjoy an evening of double the improv fun&lt;!--more--&gt; with our double feature! Two improv groups will take the stage:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dont-tou.ch&quot;&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/a&gt; - Shiitake Happens:  We don’t have mush room to advertise this show, but we assure you that a lot of shiitake will happen! And now that our mushroom puns ran out, the rest of the show will just be fun improv - Come and discover what fun adventures will unfold this time!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://basicpit.ch&quot;&gt;Basic Pitches&lt;/a&gt; - Pitch us a Musical: A musical show like no other! Basic Pitches will improvise an entire musical, complete with chart topping songs, from a few audience suggestions. Not to be missed!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><category term="guest" /><summary type="html">Come and enjoy an evening of double the improv fun</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">GAME in NARRATIVE IMPROV</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tamar-broadbent2024" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GAME in NARRATIVE IMPROV" /><published>2024-02-17T10:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-17T10:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tamar-broadbent2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tamar-broadbent2024">&lt;p&gt;Bring more comedy into your improvised stories by learning how to find and play funny patterns and endow your characters with comedic points of view!&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all love narrative improv! We take the audience on a journey and leave them feeling satisfied, knowing what’s happened to the wonderful characters we’ve just invented for them. But sometimes in narrative, we focus so hard on the story that we neglect perfect opportunities to play game along the way. We are left with ‘lulls’ – patches of silence, where we are recapping extraneous plot details, when we could be invoking raucous laughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it doesn’t have to be like this! Narrative and game can go hand in hand to make your already brilliant show pack an extra punch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drawing on my decade-long experience of performing and teaching improv, I will guide you through the principles of game and POV and show you how you can bring these techniques into your shows. You’ll find you can do so without taking away from the story you’re telling, and that it will in fact enhance the narrative, leaving the audience feeling extra thrilled at having seen a spectacle that tells them a story and delivers on the laughs throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-1&quot;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the first day, we will look at what ‘game’ is and how to discover it organically in improv scenes. We will practice using POV to give our characters a comedic engine, and also how it can be used to play game. We will look at the difference between character and POV, and you will end this day with an understanding of how to find and play funny patterns in stand-alone scenes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-2&quot;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the second day, we will bring game into narrative - improvising a structure from A to B, looking for opportunities throughout to develop strong comedic POVs, and find and play game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;requirements&quot;&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An understanding of narrative improv is useful, though not essential. (Narrative structure itself will not be taught in this class). If this is not possible, experience of improvising characters would be useful. Not suitable for absolute beginners.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="workshop" /><category term="workshop" /><summary type="html">Bring more comedy into your improvised stories by learning how to find and play funny patterns and endow your characters with comedic points of view!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The XxX’s</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/xxxs-jan2024" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The XxX’s" /><published>2024-01-20T19:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-20T19:30:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/xxxs-jan2024</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/xxxs-jan2024">&lt;p&gt;Stories about love and the end of it&lt;!--more--&gt;, inspired by expartners from the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This show on January 20th specifically will be an experimental alternative proposal as you have never seen improv before. Not on a stage but very close to the improvisers walking as spectators through different rooms. A vouyeristic tour through the intimacy of people’s spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something important to consider is that audience will be standing up through the show and due to the concept, only limited spaces are available, previous reservation through eventfrog is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This show is on donation basis. Reservation is 10chf and you can give more if you want after the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come and immerse into the intimacy of these characters.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><summary type="html">Stories about love and the end of it</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The XxX’s + musical @ Dynamo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dynamusical_2023" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The XxX’s + musical @ Dynamo" /><published>2023-12-06T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-12-06T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dynamusical_2023</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dynamusical_2023">&lt;p&gt;A double feature show&lt;!--more--&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://dont-tou.ch&quot;&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/a&gt;” will be playing an improvised show about love and breakup called “The XxX’s”.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://basicpit.ch&quot;&gt;Basic Pitches&lt;/a&gt;” will be playing an improvised musical.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><category term="guest" /><summary type="html">A double feature show</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Stranger</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-stranger2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Stranger" /><published>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-stranger2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-stranger2">&lt;p&gt;Watch the Mushrooms at improvise at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theaterida.ch/&quot;&gt;Theater Ida&lt;/a&gt; with a new long form improvised: The Stranger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet a tight knit community facing a mysterious challenge when a stranger arrives. Who are those people? What is their secret? Who is that stranger for goodness sake? We all do not know. But we will find out together with the audience. Strange times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the new long form improvised format of Don’t touch my mushrooms at Theater Ida in English.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><category term="Ida" /><summary type="html">Watch the Mushrooms at improvise at Theater Ida with a new long form improvised: The Stranger.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Stranger</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/the-stranger" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Stranger" /><published>2023-05-14T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-14T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/the-stranger</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/the-stranger">&lt;p&gt;Watch the Mushrooms at improvise at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theaterida.ch/&quot;&gt;Theater Ida&lt;/a&gt; with a new long form improvised: The Stranger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet a tight knit community facing a mysterious challenge when a stranger arrives. Who are those people? What is their secret? Who is that stranger for goodness sake? We all do not know. But we will find out together with the audience. Strange times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the new long form improvised format of Don’t touch my mushrooms at Theater Ida in English.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><category term="Ida" /><summary type="html">Watch the Mushrooms at improvise at Theater Ida with a new long form improvised: The Stranger.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Improv Earthquake</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/earthquake" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Improv Earthquake" /><published>2022-09-29T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-09-29T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/earthquake</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/earthquake">&lt;p&gt;Improv Earthquake!&lt;!--more--&gt; Cheer for your improviser to help them crush the opposition. Will your tectonic plate have the upper hand?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><summary type="html">Improv Earthquake!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Double feature</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/dobule_show" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Double feature" /><published>2022-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/dobule_show</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/dobule_show">&lt;p&gt;In this very special double feature, we present two unique improv shows in one fantastic night.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
First, Don’t Touch My Mushroom Improv will play their new improvised format “The Gathering” for the first time ever. It’s a show about a dramatic, life changing event, gathering friends and enemies, envious colleagues and backstabbing family, secret lovers and open haters. What happens at this event is a mystery to all of us. But we will find out together in “The Gathering”! With the musical support of Klearjos Papanicolaou.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But wait there’s more! The Basic Pitches, the one and only musical improv group of Zurich, will then take the stage and will perform a fully improvised musical with all its extravaganza: Singing, dancing, drama and comedy! This is their third show ever and after two grandiose shows at Theater Ida, they are playing for the first time in the city at Jenseits! With the musical support of Izaskun.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><summary type="html">In this very special double feature, we present two unique improv shows in one fantastic night.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ida Theatersport Liga</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Ida_04-2022" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ida Theatersport Liga" /><published>2022-04-29T19:30:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-29T19:30:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Ida_04-2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Ida_04-2022">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theaterida.ch/&quot;&gt;Theater Ida&lt;/a&gt; is organizing a theater sports liga with shows in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theater Ida presents the Ida Theatersport Liga. 2 teams will compete with the weapons of improvisation theatre. The audience and jury decide and award the points. It will be tough, it will be exciting, it will be emotional, it will be funny, it will be unique and unforgettable – it will be everything and much more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>{&quot;facebook&quot;=&gt;&quot;donttouchmymushroom&quot;}</name></author><category term="show" /><category term="show" /><category term="Ida" /><category term="guest" /><category term="theatersports" /><summary type="html">Theater Ida is organizing a theater sports liga with shows in English.</summary></entry></feed>