<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Don't Touch My Mushroom</title>
        <description>Don't Touch My Mushroom - </description>
        <link></link>
        <link></link>
        <lastBuildDate>2023-01-28T00:09:33+00:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2023-01-28T00:09:33+00:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Improv Earthquake</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improv Earthquake!&lt;!--more--&gt; Cheer for your improviser to help them crush the opposition. Will your tectonic plate have the upper hand?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/earthquake</link>
                <guid>/earthquake</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-09-29T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Double feature</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In this very special double feature, we present two unique improv shows in one fantastic night.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
First, Don’t Touch My Mushroom Improv will play their new improvised format “The Gathering” for the first time ever. It’s a show about a dramatic, life changing event, gathering friends and enemies, envious colleagues and backstabbing family, secret lovers and open haters. What happens at this event is a mystery to all of us. But we will find out together in “The Gathering”! With the musical support of Klearjos Papanicolaou.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But wait there’s more! The Basic Pitches, the one and only musical improv group of Zurich, will then take the stage and will perform a fully improvised musical with all its extravaganza: Singing, dancing, drama and comedy! This is their third show ever and after two grandiose shows at Theater Ida, they are playing for the first time in the city at Jenseits! With the musical support of Izaskun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/dobule_show</link>
                <guid>/dobule_show</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-06-23T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Ida Theatersport Liga</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theaterida.ch/&quot;&gt;Theater Ida&lt;/a&gt; is organizing a theater sports liga with shows in English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Theater Ida presents the Ida Theatersport Liga. 2 teams will compete with the weapons of improvisation theatre. The audience and jury decide and award the points. It will be tough, it will be exciting, it will be emotional, it will be funny, it will be unique and unforgettable – it will be everything and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/Ida_04-2022</link>
                <guid>/Ida_04-2022</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-04-29T19:30:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Theater Sports by ZIC: DTMM VS ZIC</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt; is organizing a theater sports show and they invited us to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The home team, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt;, competes in each show against a different improv group from Switzerland. The two teams improvise scenes based on audience suggestions. It is also the audience’s task to assign points to them – so YOU are in charge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s fast-paced comedy theater – spontaneous, entertaining, interactive, engaging and fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come and see it first hand to fully experience and appreciate the magic of creating theater on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/ZIC_04-2022</link>
                <guid>/ZIC_04-2022</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-04-07T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>a penny for my thoughts</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;An improvised play based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.orphicinstitute.com/&quot;&gt;a game&lt;/a&gt; where characters will try to recover their lost memories.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will ask the audience to come up with “memory triggers” to help our “patients” throughout their journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first half of the show will be short form improv games that you all know and love.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/penny</link>
                <guid>/penny</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-03-31T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Open Stage + a penny for my thoughts @ Dynamo</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tobertushabicht.ch/&quot;&gt;Tobertus Habicht&lt;/a&gt; invited us to their open stage and to premiere our new format “a penny for my thoughts”.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an english evening: In the first half there is an open stage: come, watch or jump on stage with us, you decide! We play our (and your?) favourite short-form games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the second half, we will premiere “a penny for my thoughts” an improvised play  based on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.orphicinstitute.com/&quot;&gt;a game&lt;/a&gt; where characters will try to recover their lost memories.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/dynamo</link>
                <guid>/dynamo</guid>
                <pubDate>2022-03-23T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>PREMISE + GAME in IMPROV SCENES</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you want to be able to pull ideas from an opening and use them to initiate scenes?&lt;!--more--&gt; Do you fancy yourself as having a ‘writer’s brain’ and want to channel that to make your scenes even stronger? Do you want your improv scenes to look like masterful comedy sketches?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;workshop-description&quot;&gt;Workshop description:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this two-day workshop, Tamar will introduce you to the core components of premise improv. You’ll learn how to pull an idea from a monologue and use it to initiate an improv scene, how to discover and play game with your scene partner, how to invest in the choices you and your partner make and maximise their potential and how to play believable, committed characters that you could see in a sitcom!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/tamar-broadbent</link>
                <guid>/tamar-broadbent</guid>
                <pubDate>2021-12-04T10:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>A new life!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The mushrooms are back on 2021!
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members! Come for a fantastical time full of unexpected surprises.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/new_life</link>
                <guid>/new_life</guid>
                <pubDate>2021-09-30T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improfight: Don't Touch My Mushroom VS Dodecahedron</title>
                <description>&lt;div class=&quot;massage-box alert-warning&quot;&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    &lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-exclamation-triangle&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
    This show has been cancelled due to COVID19.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We will see you on stage again in 2021!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our impro fight will set two impro groups face to face on stage and make them compete for more applause from the audience. You give us the suggestions and you vote for the troupe that gets the points!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time Don’t Touch My Mushroom will face the ETH based group Dodecahedron.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you get &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;your tickets&lt;/a&gt; beforehand. &lt;strong&gt;There are limited spaces!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-do-we-charge-for-tickets&quot;&gt;Why do we charge for tickets?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to COVID-19, we had to follow some regulations. One of them is limiting the audience to maximum 50 people and another is having everyone’s contact information (i.e. telephone number). For that the easiest and fastest solution was using a ticketing platform.  We decided to set a minimum price in order to make sure people would come to the show after having reserved a ticket. The money that is collected will be used to pay for the room and the rehearsal premises.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/fight_dodecahedron</link>
                <guid>/fight_dodecahedron</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-10-29T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Theater Sports by ZIC: DTMM VS ZIC</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt; is organizing a theater sports show and they invited us to participate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Team against team – improviser against improviser – Titan against Titan!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The home team, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zurichimprovcomedy.ch/&quot;&gt;Zurich Improv Comedy (ZIC)&lt;/a&gt;, competes in each show against a different improv group from Switzerland. The two teams improvise scenes based on audience suggestions. It is also the audience’s task to assign points to them – so YOU are in charge!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s fast-paced comedy theater – spontaneous, entertaining, interactive, engaging and fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come and see it first hand to fully experience and appreciate the magic of creating theater on the spot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/ZIC_theater_sports</link>
                <guid>/ZIC_theater_sports</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-10-08T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The Harold</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Harold is a longform improvised format which emphasises patterns, themes and group discoveries instead of a traditional plot or story. Everything starts from a simple suggestion from the audience.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
The &lt;strong&gt;Game&lt;/strong&gt; of the scene is not predetermined. We create Games and their rules in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doors open at 19:50. Show duration 20:00 - 22:00.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please make sure you get &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;your tickets&lt;/a&gt; beforehand. &lt;strong&gt;There are limited spaces!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-do-we-charge-for-tickets&quot;&gt;Why do we charge for tickets?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to COVID-19, we had to follow some regulations. One of them is limiting the audience to maximum 50 people and another is having everyone’s contact information (i.e. telephone number). For that the easiest and fastest solution was using a ticketing platform.  We decided to set a minimum price in order to make sure people would come to the show after having reserved a ticket. The money that is collected will be used to pay for the room and the rehearsal premises.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/the_harold</link>
                <guid>/the_harold</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-09-17T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>First online Improv show</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;No virus is going to prevent us from doing what we like most! Don’t Touch My Mushroom adapts to the circumstances and brings us a fully online improv show experience.&lt;!--more--&gt;
We might face a pandemic, technical difficulties and a confinement, but we hope we can bring a smile to your face when you need it most.
Join us for 30 minutes of our first attempt on virtual Improv. Let us spend part of our confinement together!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be able to access the live stream by following this link &lt;strong&gt;a few minutes before 21:00:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dont-tou.ch/online&quot;&gt;https://dont-tou.ch/online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
                <link>/first_online_show</link>
                <guid>/first_online_show</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-05-09T21:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Online workshop: One offer at a time</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;No virus is going to keep us from doing Improv! Now that most of us are secluded at home we should adapt and do things that keep us sane.&lt;!--more--&gt; I would go insane without improv and so we decided to contact international improvisers to give us workshops through VC. The first one is Stephen Thornton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;workshop-description&quot;&gt;Workshop description:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s so easy to get carried away with dialogue onstage. I’m sure we have all been there. Where we start talking and just keep going; because one idea gives way to another then another. We speak, giving out massive amounts of information. As a by-product we are also giving our partner multiple offers. Now, our partner has to make a choice as to which offer they want to go with. The choice they make might not be the one that you were wanting to explore. In this workshop we will work on delivering ONE offer at a time. One offer allows you and your partner to stay on the same page and explore what the scene is about in a deeper, clearer way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zoom link will be sent to participants via email.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/stephen</link>
                <guid>/stephen</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-03-24T19:30:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Your body can create 1001 characters!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Change your voice, play with your face, transform your attitude, your body is a formidable metamorphosing tool!.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through guided exercises based on Lecoq’s work, we will discover the power of every muscle and the thousand forms your body can take to personify characters you didn’t imagine playing. They are all at hand, let your body embodies them and let yourself incarnate playfully new ranges of characters.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/cedric2</link>
                <guid>/cedric2</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-02-23T10:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mime and object work</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This workshop focuses on a side-skill : miming and object and space work.&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having a clear vision of your environment, the objects and furnitures that are around, the size and weight of the mimes you use, is an helpful friend to make your stories more true to you, your partners and the audience. It helps you react in a more consistent way, more grounded to the reality of your scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this workshop we will train our bodies to play truly in our imaginary environments, to make them more visible to us and the audience. It finds its inspiration in Lecoq’s work, clown, commedia dell’arte.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/cedric1</link>
                <guid>/cedric1</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-02-22T10:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mushrooms on Stage</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members!
You will not walk out smarter, but you will walk out happier!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Doors open at 19:50. Show duration 20:00 -&amp;gt; 22:00.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Donation based entry –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/587330331838632/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/mushroom-on-stage</link>
                <guid>/mushroom-on-stage</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-02-20T20:00:01+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Wombats vs Mushrooms - Impro Battle</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The prophecy says that in 2020 a new generation of improv show will emerge. Only the bravest improvisers will dare challenge the mighty &lt;strong&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/strong&gt;. In this first edition, the &lt;strong&gt;Wisdom of Wombats&lt;/strong&gt; have answered the calling. Who will become the winner of the first &lt;strong&gt;Improv Battle&lt;/strong&gt;?
&lt;!--more--&gt;
– Donation based entry –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/2903070189723538/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/wombats-battle</link>
                <guid>/wombats-battle</guid>
                <pubDate>2020-01-23T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Mushroom Harvest</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Thanksgiving can be the land of any inspiration. Come for a fantastical time full of unexpected surprises. You give us suggestions and we create the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Donation based entry –&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/437628203532235/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/harvest</link>
                <guid>/harvest</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-11-13T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>IMPRO CHÄLLER presents Impro Match</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us in Improchaeller for a friendly impro contest between “Berta Pan”🍳 and “Don’t Touch My Mushroom”🍄. Crazy short forms will test their improv skills, make you laugh and wonder. You get to choose the winner!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Date: Wednesday 25 September 2019
Door opens at 19:00. Show starts at 19:30.
Location: &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/ShkY6RhFgo29BAFk7&quot;&gt;Dynamo, Zurich&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others and more info on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/2451987614884101/&quot;&gt;facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/improchaeller</link>
                <guid>/improchaeller</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-09-25T19:30:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Between 2 Worlds</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
The gap between worlds will become narrow this night. Come for a fantastical time full of unexpected surprises. You put the suggestions and we create the story.
This Summer… Don’t Touch My Mushroom, in between worlds edition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1209497019231461/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/between_two_worlds</link>
                <guid>/between_two_worlds</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-08-29T19:30:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Drawing Lines</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;19:30 Apero, 20:00 Start of the Performance&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Come and see the Mushrooms performing a new spectacle, based on Jenseits’ monthly theme: drawing lines. You have probably drawn black lines on mushrooms in the past, when you grilled them on your barbecue, but how can they draw lines on stage? And how does it work in the nature? Can a morel tell a chanterelle “hey chica, your last joke was really borderline, please stop that!”?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to see you there, for laughter, fairy tails, and pig tales (or the other way around… ) !&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will not walk out smarter, but you will walk out happier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Performance is in English&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entry: recommended contribution is 15,- chf (includes also the finger food before the show)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/386951251891130/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/crossing_lines</link>
                <guid>/crossing_lines</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-06-14T19:30:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Making Sense of Senses</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This show is based on jenseits’ seasonal theme “sense and senses.”&lt;!--more--&gt; Do mushrooms have a special sense to react and improvise on cue thrown at them? Can they smell what their fellows think? Come and discover how (un)believable stories are created in front of your eyes, based on your suggestions. All of this sprinkled with a variety of foreign accents!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Improv is what happens when the actors don’t know what will happen: A totally spontaneous spectacle, made up on the spot and based on suggestions from the audience members!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will not walk out smarter, but you will walk out happier!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 20:00 until ca. 21:30 Uhr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entrance fee: pay what you want&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/386951251891130/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/making_sense_of_senses</link>
                <guid>/making_sense_of_senses</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-04-04T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Where fungi feel at home...</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us to laugh with and at one of the few (and therefore one of the best!) Zurich’s international improv theatre troupes, Don’t Touch My Mushroom. Once again, the fungi’s show will be unscripted, unpredictable, unhinged, and inspired by you, the audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will not walk out smarter, but you will walk out happier.
&lt;!--more--&gt;
This show is based on jenseits’ seasonal theme, «Be at Home.» Do you wonder what that means for a mushroom? No worries, the players also do not know! They will make sense of it and invent (un)believable stories in front of your eyes, helped by your suggestions and their random thoughts (if they have any). All of this sprinkled with a variety of foreign accents!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time: 20:00 until ca. 21:30 Uhr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entrance fee: pay what you want&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/328722987949215/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/where_fungi_feel_at_home</link>
                <guid>/where_fungi_feel_at_home</guid>
                <pubDate>2019-02-14T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Improv Tales of 1001 Night</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Improv Tales of 1001 Night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom will be hosted on this occasion by our friends from &lt;a href=&quot;https://wombats.ch&quot;&gt;Wisdom of Wombats&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;!--more--&gt; We will create improv scenes based on real-life tales of humour, tragedy, love, different kind of stories, new fairy tales, anything with a beginning, a middle and an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;☛  Doors open 19:30, show starts at 20h.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;☛  Location: LangKult, Langstrasse 113a.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;☛  PWYW, This is a pay what you want event, a collection 🎩 will be passed around at the end of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/628596190870542/&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/wombats_mushroom</link>
                <guid>/wombats_mushroom</guid>
                <pubDate>2018-11-27T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sporeadic Fungi Improv</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us to laugh with and at one of the few (and therefore one of the best!) Zurich’s international
improv theatre troupe: The Don’t Touch my Mushroom team.&lt;!--more--&gt; Once again, the fungi’s show will be unscripted,
unpredictable, unhinged, and inspired by you, the audience. You will not walk out smarter, but you will
walk out happier. You might also learn some alternative facts created out of your suggestions and of
the players’ random neuron connections. All of this sprinkled with a variety of foreign accents!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show is in English. Also see
&lt;a href=&quot;https://jenseitsimviadukt.ch/event/improtheater-dont-touch-my-mushroom/&quot;&gt;the jenseits event page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/302342723848534/?ti=as&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/dentist_butterfly</link>
                <guid>/dentist_butterfly</guid>
                <pubDate>2018-09-25T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Wombats and Mushrooms</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Wombats and Mushrooms play together!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Join us to watch and laugh with and at two Zurich’s international improv theatre troupes playing together:
the &lt;em&gt;Wisdom of Wombats&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;https://wombats.ch&quot;&gt;https://wombats.ch&lt;/a&gt;) and the &lt;em&gt;Don’t Touch my Mushroom&lt;/em&gt; teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show is unscripted, unpredictable, unhinged, and inspired by you, the audience. You will hear epic stories about famous people that never existed, jokes so bad that they are actually good, and real good jokes. All of this created in front of your eyes and sprinkled with a variety of foreign accents!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show is in English. Please register also through
&lt;a href=&quot;https://jenseitsimviadukt.ch/event/improtheater-wombats-and-mushrooms/&quot;&gt;the jenseits event page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2701.3164958683724!2d8.52006681583793!3d47.38625731116593!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x47900a15619f4fa9%3A0x124e7e779b279679!2sjenseits+im+Viadukt!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sch!4v1529147583692&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; style=&quot;border:0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Invite others through the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/548528918877133/?ti=as&quot;&gt;Facebook event page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/wombats_mushrooms</link>
                <guid>/wombats_mushrooms</guid>
                <pubDate>2018-07-17T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>The fungus returns!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The brand new &lt;em&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/em&gt; show has arrived!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
Returning to the friendly location of &lt;strong&gt;jenseits im Viadukt&lt;/strong&gt; we will improvise
unique stories to make you laugh, cry and think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drinks are sold at the bar before the show and during the break. You are also
very welcome to stay for a drink and a chat with the talented Mushrooms - but
remember: Don’t Touch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The show is in English. Please register also through
&lt;a href=&quot;http://jenseitsimviadukt.ch/event/dont-touch-my-mushroom-the-fungus-returns/&quot;&gt;the jenseits event page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you on February 27th - the fun starts at 20:00!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/second_show</link>
                <guid>/second_show</guid>
                <pubDate>2018-02-27T20:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Premiere at Jenseits!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;The Improv Group &lt;em&gt;Don’t Touch My Mushroom&lt;/em&gt; is proud… and slightly scared… to
announce its first independent show in English!
&lt;!--more--&gt;
In a friendly atmosphere of Viadukt, we will perform some well-known and some
less so well-known improv games and try to make your face shine with a smile
throughout one dark November evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drinks will be sold at a bar. Some small snacks will be provided on spot too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to seeing you on November 7th - the fun starts at 20:00!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
                <link>/premiere_at_jenseits</link>
                <guid>/premiere_at_jenseits</guid>
                <pubDate>2017-11-07T19:00:00+00:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
